ex version
in of formula extreme meditations the
life what's my mind like that
the meeting Washington from the front
this path not a link before Nestor
White Light if teachers is the witness
also outside like in the second
[Music]
in meditation it is reported at the fourth
level I see myself as I dissolve like
the castle I had said or I
am observing what I am
Inditex start the answer that being in
Guayaquil business the answer will
start with in the fifth with the air
conditioning stepping outside line in the in
the mental state of desire scratch
the moving between the back-up soul in
the Grosby store the fantastic Jamie
Jungers page life is
constantly moving between the pop music of the
supermarket and the wonderful music of
Jimi Hendrix
[Music]
all your life
in the realm of desire is
nothing more than noticing things
march or is going deeper this little bit
to get the details
of the kiss of food
and when you start the meditation of the
realm of form management
Javitxu Barry GMT state of mind' you still
have these states still very
primitive
no  You're on a mission to be noticing the
music in the store at Goldberg, between
dancing and delving very, very, very
little, turning instead of being round
and round, stop and start and go. In the
realm of design, you don't suddenly stop
and stay if it's not like that,
already Windows Starter form. But when you
're in the rule
from this area, there are three steps that I didn't
tell you about,
but you use those two mental states
to make the transition from the mental state of
the realm
of desire of Formentera
to the mental state of the realm in the
Julius Boros form in Elche that you use.
Note it down and check in Sanskrit, in
Sanskrit, bitar, which is vital to avoid, and
from Sara Pérez for trying, mere bitar,
can managers without pointing, it's only
noticing things in your life,
bichara is delving into them
when you cross from the mental state of the
realm of desire to the one of form
and organ, Windows Mobile.
You're going to use those two for
approximately half an hour,
ward because of the meta that manages to have to
investigate because the beat arcade, the
northwest air conditioner, Arquinver, be, the
notice is not  The noise of the bid charter, the
bug is what to cut short, is to show or is to
notice the heartbeat, it
's more subtle in Richard starts @
collector who encouraged and the bug decides
that he no longer likes it arbitrarily, Diana,
besides, ERC, stop
loudly, this air conditioning, this
food, with getting to work on time,
being,
are things I no longer want, I want quieter things,
and then you enter still with a
noisy heartbeat, Artium Vitoria, after you
make the transition from Maine
Exterior Mart, the main mental state,
virtual story, the anti-interesting charal,
I'm deeply in the heart
and there aren't many, many to realize
the air conditioning and new Audis
hardware,
each of these levels has
a gadget, a gacha, which is the
Santander stock market widget, in each of these
levels has something you're rejecting, being me, I
prefer the calm sound
of my heart in I'm feeling travel and
see investments and I'm leaving behind the
air conditioning of the bid tracker, it's
Folkestone, see, was Kirchner, bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
Elbittar is
forgetting more and more about the air
conditioning, it
must be turned off,
and he's welcoming the heart
more and more.
The answer to your question when you're
in the transition from the first level
of the realm of form, English profile, the
sensations to Big Game Berdych, I
am, I became him,
you become the
heartbeat,
we can say that avoiding inhabiting, they
exist in the first level of life,
Sachs Elbittar, that it's nothing more than to realize
the era, to say that,
and he's enjoying this peace in form,
but when you move from the first level
of form to the second, and I support, but
then you release the two in Berlin,
the emotion, the sensation
is, I am my heartbeat, okay.
[Music]
In the fourth, fifth, and sixth
observer, it's not so much that the observing,
the sensations that I am inside
those, you
lose the sensation of being, of
seeing it in those levels of yesterday, and
after that, you're already inside,
Berg, and I'm in my bed